Doug, welcome to Native Dev. How are
you? Good. Hi, Simon. Thank you for
having me. Oh, absolute pleasure. And
and Doug, tell us a little bit about
yourself. Uh, sure. I've been around the
industry for hundred years and uh within
the last I'm a Microsoft MVP for 16
years and um I've been playing with AI
the current AI
since the 80s. Um well that's not
current but then just the latest uh
generative AI in the last few years and
it's just absolutely fascinated me and
uh I'm now taking it to the next chapter
the model context uh protocol MCPS. So
looking forward to presenting them
today. You obviously with the history of
that long in the AI space, you obviously
go way way deeper than any of about deep
certainly go way back.
When I say nonsense, vibe coding is
incredible fun and fit for purpose for a
specific purpose for that for that
prototyping and stuff. Uh that just
makes it that much more accessible to
people who aren't developers, people who
want disposable apps, those kind of
things. But but but you know I guess the
areas that you go into are far far more
in depth in the machine learning space.
So we're all looking forward to to
hearing uh your wisdom and talking about
MCP. So okay um Doug I'll pass over to
you. Have a great session. Thank you.
Hello everybody. Welcome. Uh my name is
Doug Frink. Uh as I mentioned to Simon
I'm going to be doing a talk on model
context protocol uh anthropics MCPS and
we'll get into that in a bit. Uh going
to have a quick slide here, then a
little bit of a demo, and then back to
slides. So I'm a 16-time Microsoft MVP.
I wrote a book called PowerShell for
Developers. And I organized the New York
City Meetup for many years, and it's now
a live stream that I do. I do multiple
ones per month. I cover all kinds of
technology, specifically uh and most
recently all in the AI space. Um I'm
actually have one coming up next week.
I'm going to do a an improv AI prompt
improv hour. So, if you want to jump
head over to that meetup, uh I'm going
to do take questions from people in the
audience and we're going to just uh live
uh prompt and see if we can solve
different kinds of problems, both
technical, marketing, whatever actually
comes up. If you uh want to stay
connected, you can find me on all the
social media platforms. I've got a
YouTube channel with lots of videos. I
do I don't like doing long videos except
for my meetups. Uh and I do lots of
little videos on MCPs. How do you
incorporate it? How do you make agentic
searches with an MCP in whatnot? There's
a recent one I put up and you can find
me over there. Cool. So, let's
uh get out of the slides and we're going
to just do some
coding. So, I'm going to bring up
uh Visual Studio Code. So, Visual Studio
Code. And if you can't see that, let me
know. I can bump up
the the font if that's good, if it's
bad. And uh so I'm going to use Visual
Studio Code. I'm going to use Visual
Studio uh GitHub Copilot in there. And
um they have a host. They they host MCPS
uh similar to Claude Desktop uh and to
have um Windsurf as well as Cursor AI do
the same thing. And what I'm going to
show here is this is how you set up a
simple um JSON config for an MCP server.
And this is similar to how you do it
inside of uh CLA desktop for example
except here I think you do you do an MCP
servers just name the Hey hey hey Doug
if you wouldn't mind if you could just
uh create if you could just enlarge the
font that would be
that would be brilliant. Thank you. I
know it's harder to I know it's harder
to code but
that work a little bigger or is that
fine? Yeah, maybe even one more but
whatever whatever hopefully works as a
as an in between. All right, this will
be fun. Maybe one less because now it's
getting all
get it just right. Cool. So, this is
basically how you do a uh an MCP server.
I'm going to do initial one. We're going
to do a standard IO. There are ones like
HTTP. You can you can do things with npx
uh all different kinds of types. And I'm
going to show you how to do one quickly
in in Python. So, I have an MC uh MCP
server.py.
Um it's really super simple and you can
do a pip install on the MCP uh fast MCP
and these are
um maintained officially and they have
uh these types of SDKs for all different
languages for TypeScript fornet
uh so on and so forth. Uh so I'm going
to actually just create two functions in
Python. Uh one is going to be called
multiply takes two variables A and B and
I'm going to have one read CSV which we
may not have time to get to. Um, so I'm
just defining the multiply as uh return
a star B. Now I'm going to go back over
here to my MCP JSON and I'm going to
click on the start. So this is going to
start up um my MCP
uh Python. I'm going to hit restart so
we can see the actual messages and the
MCP host. And this is the same thing
that again happens in uh the Windsurf
cursor and Claude desktop. It tells you
that it's starting it. it does tool
discovery um inside
of Visual Studio Code. I can click on
this toolbar and now I can see that I
have my my server with my multiply and
my read CSV tools ready to go. Now let's
see how we make that work. So once all
that's up and running. Okay. And again
you can do this with Python, TypeScript,
JavaScript.NET
net uh similar setups to invoke and to
get your tools working and you're just
basically using standard code that
you're used to. So if you're familiar
with programming in Python, you're going
to define a function just like this as
as you always have. You're going to add
a decorator and you're off to the races.
So over here now this makes my multiply
uh what they call agentic, right? And
what does that mean? So if I type over
here, what
is seven? some pick some random large
number with some decimals uh times this
number and I'm going to take that
exact what's happening now is co-pilot
inside of uh Visual Studio grabs that
and says okay I'm going to figure it
out. I can see that there's a an MCP
tool called multiply. it doesn't execute
it and it gives me the note that MCP
servers or malic uh servers or malicious
conversation content may attempt to
misuse code through these tools. Right?
If I gave you this tool, you don't you
need to do a little bit of diligence,
figure out am I trustworthy? Is my tool
trustworthy? Does it come from a third
party vendor? Does it come from a from
Anthropic or from other uh vendors that
you know of? Um, so anyway, so I found
the tool and it wants to pass those two
numbers that I just randomly chose into
the multiply and I'm going to say it
gives you the opportunity to continue.
So there is a safety feature. If I want,
I can drop this down. If I don't want to
keep answering the continue, I can say,
well, just allow for the session or for
the workspace or I can always allow
that. So there's a bunch of different
options, but you're in control. So it's
going to call my multiply tool. Nothing
fantastic going on here. Um, and it
should give me the right number. And I'm
going to copy this out hopefully
correctly. And so we get that number.
And if I come down to this uh console
here and I multiply that out, we can see
that it does it correctly. I'm going to
bounce back over into ask mode where it
doesn't use
um the MCPS in ask mode at this point, I
believe. Hopefully. I usually do this
the other way around, but let's see what
happens if I ask it. Now, it shouldn't
ask me for
MCP, it will tell me that it's going to
invoke that
tool. And always when you do live videos
with
AI, now notice it comes up with
43654, but the number is over here on
the right.
43655. Um so basically Claude sonnet
hallucinated the calculation result.
That's the reason why we use agents and
we give it tools right so that it can
actually say oh I have to do a
multiplication. Well I'm not good at
that but I'm going to use a tool for it.
And then when we use a tool
um we're golden. Okay. So I've only got
15 minutes left. So I was not going to
show you how did the M the the CSV piece
works but what that is is just it's
would would have just read the CSV the
standard uh Python piece where it opens
the file and reads in in the uh CSV and
creates a dictionary and then that what
happens is is that the m the AI here 3.7
takes my prompt my initial prompt says
oh you want to read the CSV and do
something with it then it passes that
plus all the information that comes from
the MCP tool which is the taking the
signature, the function name and the
signature and the type and the type that
it returns. Passes all that plus my
prompt into Claude Sonic. Claude Sonic
says, "Oh, I need to call a a function."
Tells the host, the Visual Studio Code
host or whichever one you're using, hey,
you need to go make this function call.
It does that. That's where the continue
pops up. it does that action and then it
takes the results of reading the CSV
file and brings it back into the
conversation so that Claude Sonic can go
oh now I know what's going on in this
particular file and I'm ready to go. So
that's just a quick overview uh or a
quick run through of uh an
MCP and of course that could
be at least a two-hour presentation. Um
so let's talk a little bit about well
what MCPs are right a universal
interface for AI native development.
Um so it's an open protocol. MCP is an
open protocol for connecting AI models
to tools and to data. That was what I
was just showing you right it connected
to a multiply. I would have demoed how
it connected to data and it would have
been a CSV but it's not limited to that
right. So if I wanted to connect it to
um a SQL server database or to Cosmos DB
or SQL light or
Postgress, I may have code that already
does that, right? maybe already
authenticates and authorize is a and I
can authorize and authenticate through
my cap my code to those those database
to those data to backends and then they
can now as tools play into the AI model
space
um via the MCP protocol. So it's JSON
based, works over uh standard IO, HTTP
or SSE, right? So there's a whole bunch
of different ways. And again, so you can
think of uh HTTP and SSE as being uh
remote servers on uh or things on the
internet that you can tap into. And
what's cool is when I talked about
grabbing a Python function and taking
its signature, the name of the function,
the name of all the parameters, the
types that all the parameters are
defined at, and how what's going to get
returned as a type from the from the
function call. That's describing the
tool capabilities and that gets set up
in a specific way that get hand gets
handed from the MCP server back into the
MCP host and then models invoke them
like APIs. There's no SDKs involved, no
plugins, no retraining required. You saw
me, I just had a little Python function.
I put a decorator on it from the SDK and
I told and I created a fiveline uh
mcp.json config. Hit start and I'm ready
to go. This is standardized by Anthropic
and it's being adopted by Microsoft and
OpenAI, Google's and everybody else. All
right.
So the multi-host one protocol every
interface everything from like idees
like I mentioned uh Windsurf Visual
Studio Code um cursor CLIs like uh Ader
and Klein uh and edge devices. It's all
the same contract for all of these. The
host speaks JSON. Again, there's no
SDKs, no friction, and you learn how to
build your stuff once and then you can
reuse it everywhere.
Um, and your tools follow your team, not
your tech, right? So, it's if people
want to use um Jet Brains, they I
believe they now have a MCP host, which
is not difficult to write. So, for these
uh companies to build them into their
tools, there's not a difficult process.
So, if it's not here, it'll be here very
soon. Um, and you know, this isn't just
crossplatform. It's cross
mindset. Wherever your devs go, the
protocol protocol goes with them. Um,
and and for me, I know this smells a
little bit like the old Java pitch, you
know, write once, run anywhere, and then
you added the extra piece of test
forever. This is not the same thing. Um,
it's not about by code, it's not about
virtual machines, you know, it's not
about where the code runs. It's about
how tools talk and making that
conversation
universal. Cool. So, let's talk about
some key uses for M uh MCPS. AI coding
assistance access entire code bases,
docs, and dev tools via Git, GitHub, MCP
servers. Um, better autocomplete, PR
reviews, and refactors. And that's just
one of the pieces of the AI coding
assistance. Like I mentioned before, you
can do with data. So, there are pieces
out of all these large companies that
let you integrate with your uh SQL
Server backends. Um, Microsoft's letting
it integrate with the Azure and Au, uh,
Amazon's following along as well. In
terms of enterprise workflows, they have
uh, pieces now from that can integrate
uh, with uh, Jira, Confluence. Zapier
has this free. You can go up today and
you look for Zapier MCP uh, and you can
find a way to for free to turn on some
of their tools and then it uses the SSE
interface. So, as you saw me define the
Python one, you just change the type to
SSE, you put a URL in, and now you're
connected to Zapier. And if you get more
involved with the Zapier side, like if
you want to do Google Sheets or your
Google email, yes, you have to
authenticate and give that those
credentials to it to make it work. Very
simple though, straightforward. It's
worth checking out. And then AI can read
and write tickets, summarize docs,
trigger workflows. And this is what the
third party companies are doing. And
it's great to take a look because then
you get ideas of well what can I
integrate? What code do I have that I'd
like to integrate to my uh daily flow
whether it be in your company or
personal data and analytics NLP to SQL.
So you can now prompt to SQL and these
MCPs are really cool because it's got it
does real time schemas. So you can say,
"Hey, here's my database." And the first
thing it does when you say, "Show me how
many albums sold in, you know, 2020 that
were more than this." And the amount of
time that it played was an hour and a
half. The first thing it does is it goes
out, checks the schema of your entire
database. Um, and you
can you can uh hone it down to just this
set of uh tables. It figures out the
schema and then from that the the AI the
AI models can really in you know it just
figures out what foreign keys what
constraints and whatnot so you can
actually do it can construct the SQL
that you need um in a really accurate
way and this works with Postgress and
MySQL um and MCP host can analyze live
business data or indexes like elastic
search what else web and external info
so AI uses web search via MCP I just put
up a video on how how I put that
together. Um it's not there's a few
lines of code and it's done. Uh uses web
search to pull live info or automate web
actions dynamic real-time context.
Right? So if you're familiar with uh
chat GPT web, you can ask questions and
click the search button or it knows how
to go out to the web to gather
information today, not just based on the
training date that it was cut off.
persistent context accesses files,
projects, notes or vector stores via MCP
enabling long-term memory and continuity
across SE uh sessions and that's just
some of the things it can do right so
the persistent context it can actually
do certain types of improved rag
capabilities retrieval augmented
generation so what it unlocks less glue
more flow right protocol first no SDK
friction um you didn't see me use an SDK
I started up standard Python with fast
MCP P I annotated one of my functions,
clicked start, and I was it was now part
of the host's AI flow. It's one
interface uh reused by devs and AI
assistants and exposed tools via HTTP or
standard IO in minutes. It builds
towards an agentic workflow without
upfront complexity. Um, and yes, so
depending on if I'm asking questions to
my CSV file, if it doesn't get the
answer that it wants, it'll prompt it'll
go back and reread the file or look at
more information in it and it will
figure it'll take multi uh steps to and
multi turns to figure out is it
answering the question that I asked. So,
and this could be any of your tools. So,
it gets really interesting. Governance
and trust, agility without chaos. Um,
lots of stuff going on in in in you saw
when I hit the continue, that's host
mediated permissions. you you explicitly
approve tool usage. There's auditing is
optional. Some and many of the uh
vendors are now coming out with ways
that it turns on automatically for
certain pieces and then you can opt in
or opt out of others. Um and then you
can figure that out for your own code
that you're providing. Uh maybe you're
going to provide a thirdparty tool. Um
and there's a lot of vendor
collaboration, right? Anthropic,
Microsoft, and OpenAI and Google are
working on a lot of the standards. One
of the papers were just put up by MCP
today. uh where this is going. I think
next week there's another uh conference,
the uh the dev MCP conference, and
they're going to be talking a lot about
this and the players that are actually
doing the work on this. Um emerging
security patterns, prompt injection,
defense, endpoint control. So, this is
the this is being treated very seriously
and lots of big brains are working on
it. Where's it going? It's not a
framework. It's a foundation we're at
with this um from VS Code to claude to
no code, right? So, Zapier, Claude
desktop, VS Code, Windsurf, all these
different pieces. Uh there's a bunch of
tools inside of Azure now that are MCP
host. I believe Fabric is one of them.
So, you can plug these tools in there.
Uh and you go from run this tool to own
the loop, right? So, you own what's
going on in the AI uh flow and you get
to choose to say continue or not. And if
you're building for this, you have even
more control over it. Uh build, fix,
deploy, no handoffs, right? You can just
uh let your model do it or you can do it
within your code. Um so you have lots of
ways to architect, many degrees of
freedom to get this done. So MCP is how
we wire agents into the real world. Um
so this shift is not just about running
tools. Um it's it's about building tools
without asking uh for glue at every
step. And again, you saw what I did with
one function. It's that simple. We may
have to rewrite a bunch of code. Um you
certainly need to learn how to do prompt
engineering uh and understand what data
is actually being sent in the context
through the MCP tool annotation, how
your function and parameters and so on
are being handed off so it plays better
into your context. So when you ask
questions or your user asks questions,
things can be figured
out. So MCP is how we stop talking about
agents and start building with them. Um
this is my last slide and just to say
that in the span of a year, so I think
this was dropped like in November of of
2024. So in less than a year, MCPS have
catalyzed a flurry of developer
creativity uh by offering a unified way
to extend models with tools and data.
MCP has been key to unlocking novel
applications from coding co-pilots that
understand entire code bases to uh
enterprise bots that juggle multiple uh
business apps to assistants that can
analyze real databases and agents that
browse the web or maintain long-term
memory. And there are other products out
there. Rue Ro is uh he uh heavily
leveraging MCPS to great effect. um and
learning how to build these kind of
things, learning how to eval these uh
types of systems. That is really what
you need to unlock this journey. So, I
don't know how how am I on
time? Oh, we got a couple of more
minutes, but yeah, I got a couple more
minutes. We have some questions as well.
Great. Let's uh I try I figured I'd rush
because I didn't see the clock. So, uh
let's answer some questions if we can.
Awesome. Yeah. Um so one question
um around manual vetting. Um so Frank
here uh asks manualing of an MCP is
certainly not scalable but ignoring
warings warnings is dangerous. Any
suggestions for fine grained MCP ACL?
Good question. Um so as I've even I've
been talking about and presenting on AI
since late 2022, right?
And your job as a developer does not end
just because you can copy and paste
something out of a AI chat. It's the
same challenge we had back with Stack
Overflow as well as Google. You didn't
just copy stuff you found, drop it in
your editor, compile, and give it to
production. You've got to vet it. You
got to do the testing. This is not a
magic bullet. This is a tool that you
need to learn to leverage. And the more
you use it, the more you internalize how
it works, the the faster you'll go with
it. Uh because you'll be able to trust
it more. Um, in terms of ales, like I
mentioned in the governance, next week
they're going to be talking about it.
Microsoft will be at that dev summit and
they'll be talking about how you can
hook it up to um, Entra and you can do
they're doing single sign uh, SSO type
stuff with these pieces. So you this is
not going to run rampid and crazy over
your systems. Um, so yes, they're
thinking about it. Those are the people
that got paid the high pay the big bucks
to solve these problems. I'm very
confident. you know, Anthropic doesn't
want this to come out in the first day.
You turn it on and it takes over your
enterprise, right? And and that's a
that's a real like important important
thing because I guess the the followup
here was how do we confirm that the
capabilities
um text is actually accurate to what
it's actually trying to deliver and not
malicious. So, I guess we we're probably
hitting a lot of the same problems that
we saw if you look back into the SCA
world in and around uh you know,
malicious third party libraries. Um I
guess from that point of view is that
there's a there's an extra step which
perhaps um we're not quite there with
MCPS where uh you kind of like have that
um
uh that dependency graph. Uh I'm not
sure we're quite there yet with the MCP
graph. No, we're not there. But the good
thing is when you even take a look at
npm libraries in open source, right,
that always was a big problem like hey
right we were very afraid in the
enterprise space to bring it in open
source. So you have to vet that. What
does it mean to vet it? Who get who's
responsible if it breaks? It's the same
thing where we are. Again, this is not a
magic bullet. Just because it's AI, this
is not science fiction. Um, if you don't
do diligence, that's going to be a
problem. But that's nothing new with us
as with software tools.
Yeah. Excellent. Um couple of people
here uh Frank one of them Michael the
other um is MTP just a higher level rest
uh so or even ask uh remote function
remote function calls and I think
there's a lot of similarities
um what's your take on that absolutely I
mean and it's good to draw these
analogies towards these other systems
but again they're analogies they're not
what it actually is so in terms of rest
calls and and remote function calls
absolutely but what this does is that
through the simple MCPJ JSON spec that
you're giving into the host, you're now
including what you've done, right? So,
you can even wire up your remote
function call or your other REST AP APIs
into give it to a rest to define what
your tool does and now it's going to
play into an MCP host that does all the
AI interaction for you and just calls
you when it thinks it needs to. I don't
know if that helps. So it's an So you
we're not and that's the beauty of all
this. We're not learning something new.
We're taking all we're learning is oh I
want to annotate my power my uh Python
function this way and now I can play
into the MCP space and anything that's
has an MCP host I my code now works in
it. That's crazy. Um, but it doesn't
matter if your code is a function, a
remote function, an Azure function, a
lambda and a and Amazon. Um, or it's
another set of REST APIs that now you
can start bringing those together. Now,
you need to understand prompt
engineering and if you're giving it too
much context like, oh, I've got like 60
REST endpoints. Let me just wrap those
in. Well, the AI is going to get
confused like you do. Which one do I
pick? When do I pick it? Why do I pick
it? Um, how did you name your functions?
How did you name your parameters? what
kind of help documentation and just a
little snippet of what this thing does
um becomes very important because that
becomes part of your context which is
basically just an enlarged prompt. So I
don't know if that's helps. Yeah. No
questions. Yeah, there's another good
one here actually around um the
difference between MCP and A2A because I
feel
like MCP seems MCP seems to have got so
much of the news um and it's like the
buzz word. A2A is quite similar though,
right? And but but doesn't seem to be uh
doesn't seem to be taking off quite as
much. What's that? What's the
difference? Well, that's a great good
point. Again, MCPs dropped in November.
A 80 AD 80A just dropped in the last
month. So, let's give it a little bit of
time. And they're they're very
different. So, agent to agent is really
um so if you build an agent, it's not an
it could be something that's across the
wire. It could be a remote MCP server.
So it really helps you orchestrate
multiple agents in different uh spaces,
right? Whereas MCP is local to the
process that's running it, whether it's
an IDE or whether it's a um uh an
ecosystem inside of one of the cloud
providers, things like that. Uh as but
keep an eye on the agent agent because
that's Google dropped some really good
stuff there. Yeah. Yeah. Awesome. Um I
don't see any new uh comments in. I
think we've had quite a few great
questions there. Um yeah, I mean
actually just on that point actually of
the fact that
um you know what did we say November did
you say MC Anthropic dropped MCP? Yeah.
And then in the last month 808 this is
technology that really hasn't been
around for for long at all yet the the
that's an understatement. The adoption
seems it's bizarre how how how fast that
adoption's been. Um when I looked at
MCPs and I we can talk about the
authentication in a second. when I
looked at NC um you know I played around
with custom GPTs in OpenAI and they were
going to build a store and you could
build your own and it was really cool
and I played around with a bunch of it
and uh then they kind of decided to back
off from that all of a sudden. So when I
saw Anthropic put out um MCPS, I just
thought, "Ah, that's just another custom
GPT." And I was and and everybody it was
just and like, you know, it wasn't from
my own in, you know, I didn't, it's not
that I looked into it and went, "Wow,
this is amazing." It was like I just
heard, you know, again, I'm an MVP, so I
just hear things different from
different channels that others don't.
And I was like, "What is going on?" And
uh so yeah, and it the entire AI space
is crazy. We're going from monthly to
weekly announcements on new user
experiences, developer experiences,
models getting better. We're going to be
going to a daily. So, and these things,
what we're seeing is going to be crazy.
So, authentication in MCP. Um, yep.
That's why I mentioned Entra ID. It's
basically Microsoft's AD. uh and they
anthropic and whatnot will be out at the
conference next week and they're doing
uh there's a uh GitHub repo that they're
working on in the anthropic uh GitHub
space. Uh you can follow along with the
RFC's and whatnot and they're they're
they're building it in and uh they're
building it in the open and they got the
top people working on it. They know it
needs to be solved and I'm confident
that I'm confident they're going to
solve it because I know I'm not going
to. Um, so it's not it's not there yet,
but don't let that dissuade you because
you want to sit back and try these
locally. So you want you begin to learn
the process so you can internalize what
is happens when I when I build these
things and I connect them together and
how does the model work? It's a whole,
right? It's like learning new third
party tools like we talked about
earlier. Yeah. Yeah. And and I think
that's probably a good a good way to
kind of like uh talk about this
whereby you know without those without
those kind of production level things
that we need to be there to make sure
that we're secure. This is more in the
in the level of let's see what we can
do. Let's play with it but recognize you
know what what is lacking today in
making this you know truly production
grade uh quality that we can rely on. Um
but but certainly these things are
coming I'm sure particularly given how
much how much uh people are are
investing in in in playing around with
these and you know the sheer number of
MCP servers around that people are
building it's there's going to be an
amount of time whereby uh we just need
to switch that on I guess in in more
productive well well also I mean when we
talk about authentication in MCP just
like the early days of uh GPT3 right we
were we were learn I was learning from
some of some of the great AI model uh
the ML and AI folks that were like, "Oh,
guess what? If you structure your if you
structure your prompt with JSON in the
front, have your question and put JSON
at the end, you can get these amazing
capabilities." Well, OpenAI went back to
the table and they trained the models
based on that that that type of
research. So, we can do the MCP
authentication ourselves today. You
don't need to wait for everybody. It's
not there's nothing. It's just code,
right? So, you can actually build that
into your function or whatever you're
building. you're just getting called as
a function as a function from the AI
from the MCP host. So there's nothing
it's just different way of doing uh
calls into your program or to your
endpoints to your API to your SDK. The
rest you can handle, but we're going to
be able to offload that once the adu
authentication comes online for all the
different pe all the different uh places
and that's why they're going to
standardize it. But you that you know
it's not it's just code, right? And
it's, you know, I've built these agent
systems myself without lang chain and
all that kind of stuff where, you know,
I'm building my own loop and I'm knowing
when the model saying, "Hey, I need a
fun, you need to call this function."
And I do the function call in my code
and then return the result. It's a loop
feedback and knowing when to do it and
when to stop, right? So it's not and
then also they come out with MCPs does
it do it for you. Awesome. And it does
it even better because they have the
geniuses working on. So there's nothing
there's nothing. It's just I hate to say
it, it's just it's just code and it's
has access to an LLM and they're just
making it easier so you can get your job
done. Awesome. Well, that's a great
that's a great way to end the session
there, Doug. And and thank you very very
much for the session. It was very very
insightful and I think this is
definitely a hot topic right now even in
the even in the hot bucket that is AI.
So thank you very much for giving the
session. Thank you Simon. Been a
pleasure.